The next part of the flamingo you're going to do is his beak.
You're going to take out your striping brush, the black one, and wipe off as much polish as you can.
You want to make sure that there's really just enough polish on there to do the beak.
At the very tip of your head, you're going to do very small 'V' shape.
That's going to give you the beak to your flamingo.
You're going to do that to each nail.
Doesn't have to be an open 'V', it can be a little closed.
Just want to kind of go right along the outside of the pink there, to kind of give the shape of his beak.
That's just going to come down into a small point.
Again, you want to make sure that your polish isn't too dry on your striper brush.
That way, it doesn't get stringy and then mess up your design.
Once you've gotten the 'V' on all four, for the beaks, you're ready to go to the next part of your design.
But that is how you do the beak to the flamingo.